erank.com 2000-12-02

# eRank.com Privacy Policy

## Privacy Statement for eRank.com Dating Music & Fashion Forums

**eRank.com Dating Music & Fashion Forums **has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [eRank.com Dating Music & Fashion Forums](http://www.erank.com/)

#### Information Automatically Logged

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.  This information may be used to refine the marketing strategy and product selection for this site. 

#### Advertisers

We use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we do not use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad companies, and we do not have access to this information.

We have ads served onto our site by Advertising.com. To visit their privacy statement, please click here:  
<http://www.advertising.com/privacy/index.html>.

Some ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by our Web advertising partner, Sonar Network, using DoubleClick's DART technology.  In the course of delivering an ad to you, our advertising partner collects certain non-personally identifiable information about you. If you would like to know more about the information gathering practices and "opt-out" procedures of Sonar Network, please click here:  
<http://www.sonar.com/content/privacy.htm>

#### Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted.

Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes.

#### External Links

This site contains links to other sites. **eRank.com Dating Music & Fashion Forums **is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### Special Relationships

This site has special relationships - such as "Powered by" partners, content providers, business partners, cobranded sites - with other sites. **eRank.com Dating Music & Fashion Forums **is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

#### Security

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

#### Children's Guidelines

We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children: 

  1. We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.
  2. We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, message boards, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent
  3. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to: 
    1. Respond directly to the child's request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.
    2. Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.
    3. Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.
  4. We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.
  5. We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.
  6. We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.
  7. We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.
  8. We will encourage children to get their parent's permission before sharing personal information online.

## Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can click here.
